Guide to the System Development Foundation (Palo Alto, Calif.) Records, 1957-1993
Department of Special Collections
- Series 2. Research Program Files
  - Subseries A. Grants Awarded
    - Subsubseries 2. Grant Program files
      - B. Grant Products files
        - G004, Rand Corporation, #61982-1987 (Box 45, Folder 6)
        - G004, Rand Corporation, #71982-1987 (Box 45, Folder 7)
        - G004, Rand Corporation, #81982-1987 (Box 45, Folder 8)
        - G004, Rand Corporation, #91982-1987 (Box 45, Folder 9)
        - G004, Rand Corporation, #101982-1987 (Box 45, Folder 10)
        - G004c, Rand Corporation, #11988 (Box 45, Folder 11)
        - G004c, Rand Corporation, #21988 (Box 46, Folder 1)
        - G004c, Rand Corporation, #31988 (Box 46, Folder 2)
        - G004c, Rand Corporation, #41988 (Box 46, Folder 3)
        - G004c, Rand Corporation, #51988 (Box 46, Folder 4)
        - G004c, Rand Corporation, #61988 (Box 46, Folder 5)
        - G004c, Rand Corporation, #71988 (Box 46, Folder 6)
        - G013b, Gerstein, George. Papers, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 1)
        - G013b, Gerstein, George. Papers, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 2)
        - G013a, Gerstein, George. Papers, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 3)
        - G013d, Gerstein, George. Book review, 1987. (Box 47, Folder 4)
        - G015, Waterman, Michael S. Mathematical Methods for DNA Sequences #11987 (Box 47, Folder 5)
        - G015, Waterman, Michael S. Mathematical Methods for DNA Sequences #21987 (Box 47, Folder 6)
        - G015, Waterman, Michael S. Mathematical Methods for DNA Sequences #31987 (Box 47, Folder 7)
        - G015, Waterman, Michael S. Mathematical Methods for DNA Sequences #41987 (Box 47, Folder 8)
        - G015, Waterman, Michael S. Mathematical Methods for DNA Sequences #51987 (Box 47, Folder 9)
        - G015, Waterman, Michael S. Mathematical Methods for DNA Sequences #61987 (Box 47, Folder 10)
        - G015, Waterman, Michael S. Mathematical Methods for DNA Sequences #71987 (Box 47, Folder 11)
        - G015, Waterman, Michael S. Mathematical Methods for DNA Sequences #81987 (Box 47, Folder 12)
        - G015, Waterman, Michael S. Mathematical Methods for DNA Sequences #91987 (Box 47, Folder 13)
        - G015, Waterman, Michael S. Papers, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 14)
        - G015, Waterman, Michael S. Papers #11987 (Box 47, Folder 15)
        - G015, Waterman, Michael S. Papers #21987 (Box 48, Folder 1)
        - G015, Waterman, Michael S. Papers #31987 (Box 48, Folder 2)
        - G015a, Waterman, Michael S. Papers, 1984 (Box 48, Folder 3)
        - G015, Waterman, Michael S. Papers, #11985 (Box 48, Folder 4)
        - G015, Waterman, Michael S. Papers, #21985 (Box 48, Folder 5)
        - G015, Waterman, Michael S. Papers, #31985 (Box 48, Folder 6)
        - G015, Waterman, Michael S. Papers, #41985 (Box 48, Folder 7)
        - G015, Waterman, Michael S. Papers, #51985 (Box 48, Folder 8)
        - G015, Waterman, Michael S. Manuscript to appear in Annals of Probability (Box 48, Folder 9)
        - G015, Waterman, Michael S. Paper, c. 1983; Thomas H. Byers, Ph.D. thesis, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 10)
        - G015[a or c], Waterman, Michael S. Papers, 1987 and undated (Box 48, Folder 11)
        - G015b, Waterman, Michael S. Paper, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 12)
        - G015b, Waterman, Michael S. Annual report, Part II #1Sept. 1985-Aug. 1986 (Box 49, Folder 1)
        - G015b, Waterman, Michael S. Annual report #2Sept. 1985-Aug. 1986 (Box 49, Folder 2)
        - G015b, Waterman, Michael S. Annual report #3Sept. 1985-Aug. 1986 (Box 49, Folder 3)
        - G015c, Waterman, Michael S.. Papers #11985 (Box 49, Folder 4)
        - G015c, Waterman, Michael S. Papers #21985 (Box 49, Folder 5)
        - G015c, Waterman, Michael S. Papers, 1987-1988 (Box 49, Folder 6)
        - G015c, Waterman, Michael S. Priscilla Jean Morris, thesis, Aug. 1985 (Box 49, Folder 7)
        - G015c, Waterman, Michael S. Robert Bruce Waltman, thesis, May 1985 (Box 49, Folder 8)
        - G015c, Waterman, Michael S. Annual report, included papers #11983 (Box 49, Folder 9)
        - G015c, Waterman, Michael S. Annual report #21983 (Box 49, Folder 10)
        - G015c, Waterman, Michael S. Annual report #31983 (Box 49, Folder 11)
        - G015c, Waterman, Michael S. Annual report #41983 (Box 49, Folder 12)
        - G015c, Waterman, Michael S. Annual report, included papers #11984 (Box 50, Folder 1)
        - G015c, Waterman, Michael S. Annual report #21984 (Box 50, Folder 2)
        - G015c, Waterman, Michael S. Annual report #31984 (Box 50, Folder 3)
        - G015c, Waterman, Michael S. Annual report #41984 (Box 50, Folder 4)
        - G023, Fateman, Richard J. Papers, 1983 (Box 50, Folder 5)
        - G023, Fateman, Richard J. Papers, 1984 (Box 50, Folder 6)
        - G023, Fateman, Richard J. John K. Foderaro, thesis, 1983 (Box 50, Folder 7)
        - G023, Fateman, Richard J. Background information for site visit #1Aug. 1983 (Box 50, Folder 8)
        - G023, Fateman, Richard J. Background information for site visit #2Aug. 1983 (Box 50, Folder 9)
        - G023, Fateman, Richard J. Background information for site visit #3Aug. 1983 (Box 50, Folder 10)
        - G028b, Sproull, Lee. Papers, 1983-1984 (Box 50, Folder 11)
        - G028b, Sproul Lee. Papers,1985 (Box 50, Folder 12)
        - G028b, Sproul Lee. Papers,1986 (Box 51, Folder 1)
        - G028b, Sproull, Lee. Chalkboards and BBoards, draft, ch. 1-4Aug. 1986 (Box 51, Folder 2)
        - G028b, Sproull, Lee. Chalkboards and BBoards, draft, ch. 5-9Aug. 1986 (Box 51, Folder 3)
        - G028b, Sproul Lee. Chalkboards and BBoards, ch. 10-endAug. 1986 (Box 51, Folder 4)
        - G028b, Sproul Lee. Chalkboards and BBoards, draft preface, July 1986 (Box 51, Folder 5)
        - G049, Resch, Ronald. "E & S and NYIT, 3rd Generation Dup." (Box 51, Folder 6)
          (videocassette filed in Video Box 1 shelved at end of Series II)
        - G055a, Cowan, Jack. Papers, 1972-1979 and undated (Box 51, Folder 7)
        - G057b, Simmons, James. Papers, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 8)
        - G057b, Simmons, James. Papers, 1987 and undated (Box 51, Folder 9)
        - G058[a-b], Sowizral, Henry. Automatic Generation of Compilers and Interpreters,1982 (Box 51, Folder 10)
        - G058[a-b], Sowizral, Henry. Arthur Paul Goldberg, thesis, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 11)
        - G058[a-b], Sowizral, Henry. Behrokh Samadi, dissertation, #11985 (Box 52, Folder 1)
        - G058[a-b], Sowizral, Henry. Behrokh Samadi, dissertation, #21985 (Box 52, Folder 2)
        - G113, Schwartz, Jacob. Papers, 1980 and undated (Box 52, Folder 3)
        - G113, Schwartz, Jacob. NYU Computer Science Department Technical Reports,Apr.-Sept. 1982 (Box 52, Folder 4)
        - G113, Schwartz, Jacob. NYU Computer Science Department Technical Reports, Feb.-Mar. 1983 (Box 52, Folder 5)
        - G113, Schwartz, Jacob. NYU Robotics Research Technical Reports, Mar.-Dec. 1983 (Box 52, Folder 6)
        - G113, Schwartz, Jacob. NYU Robotics Research Technical Reports, Apr.-June 1984 (Box 52, Folder 7)
        - G113[a-b], Schwartz, Jacob. Meeting agendas, June-Aug. 1986 (Box 52, Folder 8)
        - G113b, Schwartz, Jacob. Papers, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 9)
        - G117, Raibert, Marc. Tutorial on Robotics--In Principal and Practice (Box 52, Folder 10)
          1981
        - G117, Raibert, Marc. "3D Balance in Hopping" (videocassette filed in Video Box 1 shelved at end of Series II) (Box 52, Folder 11)
        - G117, Raibert, Marc. "Walking Machine Video" (videocassette filed in Video Box 1 shelved at end of Series II) (Box 52, Folder 12)
        - G117, Raibert, Marc. Dynamically Stable Legged Locomotion, report1983 (Box 53, Folder 1)
        - G117, Raibert, Marc. Dynamically Stable Legged Locomotion, report1985-1986 (Box 53, Folder 2)
        - G117a, Raibert, Marc. Papers (Box 53, Folder 3)
          Oct. 1982-Oct. 1983
        - G117a, Raibert, Marc. Papers (Box 53, Folder 4)
          Nov. 1983-Dec. 1984
        - G117a, Raibert, Marc. Dynamically Stable Legged Locomotion, report1985 (Box 53, Folder 5)
        - G117b, Raibert, Marc. "Symmetry in Running," 1986 (Box 53, Folder 6)
        - G136, Roth, Bernard. Atul Bajpai, thesis, Dec. 1984 (Box 53, Folder 7)
        - G136, Roth, Bernard. Papers, 1985 (Box 53, Folder 8)
        - G136a, Roth, Bernard. Papers, #11985-1986 (Box 54, Folder 1)
        - G136a, Roth, Bernard. Papers, #21985-1986 (Box 54, Folder 2)
        - G136a, Roth, Bernard. John James Craig, dissertation, June 1986 (Box 54, Folder 3)
        - G136a, Roth, Bernard. Ashitava Ghosal, dissertation, Aug. 1986 (Box 54, Folder 4)
        - G136a, Roth, Bernard. John J. Craig, Introduction to Robotics, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 5)
        - G229, Scacchi, Walter. Papers, 1986-1987 (Box 54, Folder 6)
        - G230, American Academy of Arts and Sciences. Computerized bibliography manual #1 (Box 54, Folder 7)
        - G230, American Academy of Arts and Sciences. Computerized bibliography manual #2 (Box 54, Folder 8)
        - G230, American Academy of Arts and Sciences. Computerized bibliography manual #3 (Box 54, Folder 9)
        - G230, American Academy of Arts and Sciences. Computerized bibliography manual #4 (Box 54, Folder 10)
        - G230, American Academy of Arts and Sciences. Computerized bibliography manual, diskettes (Box 55, Folder 1)
        - G230, American Academy of Arts and Sciences. Computerized bibliography manual, print copy, Section I A (Box 55, Folder 2)
        - G230, American Academy of Arts and Sciences. Computerized bibliography manual, print copy, Section I B (Box 55, Folder 3)
        - G230, American Academy of Arts and Sciences. Computerized bibliography manual, print copy, Sections II A and B (Box 55, Folder 4)
        - G230, American Academy of Arts and Sciences. Computerized bibliography manual, print copy, Sections II C-F (Box 55, Folder 5)
        - G235[a-c], Hinton, Geoffrey. Annual report1983 (Box 55, Folder 6)
        - G235[a-c], Hinton, Geoffrey. Annual report1984 (Box 55, Folder 7)
        - G235[a-c], Hinton, Geoffrey. Papers, #11984-1985 (Box 56, Folder 1)
        - G235[a-c], Hinton, Geoffrey. Papers, #21984-1985 (Box 56, Folder 2)
        - G237, Mead, Carver. Papers, 1981. (Box 56, Folder 3)
        - G237, Mead, Carver. David L. Johannsen, Silicon Compilation, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 4)
        - G237, Mead, Carver. Marina Chien-mei Chen, Space-Time Algorithms: Semantics and Methodology,1983 (Box 56, Folder 5)
        - G237a, Mead, Carver. Final report #11985 (Box 56, Folder 6)
        - G237a, Mead, Carver. Final report #21985 (Box 56, Folder 7)
        - G237a, Mead, Carver. Final report #31985 (Box 56, Folder 8)
        - G237[a-b], Mead, Carver. Supplemental papers, 1982-1984 (Box 57, Folder 1)
        - G237[a-b], Mead, Carver. Sally A. Browning, The Tree Machine: A Highly Concurrent Computing Environment, 1980 (Box 57, Folder 2)
        - G237[a,b,c], Mead, Carver. Papers #11985-1988 (Box 57, Folder 3)
        - G237[a,b,c], Mead, Carver. Papers #21985-1988 (Box 57, Folder 4)
        - G237[a,b,c], Mead, Carver. Papers #31985-1988 (Box 57, Folder 5)
        - G237b, Mead, Carver. David I. Feinstein, Relating Thermodynamics to Information Theory (thesis), May 1986 (Box 57, Folder 6)
        - G237c, Mead, Carver. Introduction to VLSI Systems, 1980 (Box 57, Folder 7)
        - G238a, Pine, Jerome. CALTECH Biology Annual Report, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 1)
        - G240, Kamp, Hans and Stanley Peters. Situations in Discourse (draft), part 1 (Box 58, Folder 2)
        - G240, Kamp, Hans and Stanley Peters. Situations in Discourse (draft) part 2 (Box 58, Folder 3)
        - G240, Kamp, Hans and Stanley Peters. Situations in Discourse (draft) part 3 (Box 58, Folder 4)
        - G240, Kamp, Hans and Stanley Peters. John Barwise and John Perry, manuscript, part 1 (Box 58, Folder 5)
        - G240, Kamp, Hans and Stanley Peters. John Barwise and John Perry, manuscript, part 2 (Box 58, Folder 6)
        - G241, Sejnowski, Terrence. Papers, 1982-1984 (Box 58, Folder 7)
        - G241, Sejnowski, Terrence. Papers, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 8)
        - G241, Sejnowski, Terrence. Annual report, included papers1983 (Box 58, Folder 9)
        - G242a, Hewitt, Carl. William Arthur Kornfield, dissertation, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 1)
        - G242[a-d], Hewitt, Carl. Papers, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 2)
        - G242[a-d], Hewitt, Carl. Papers #11983 (Box 59, Folder 3)
        - G242[a-d], Hewitt, Carl. Papers #21983 (Box 59, Folder 4)
        - G242[a-d], Hewitt, Carl. Papers, 1984-1988 (Box 59, Folder 5)
        - G243, Zue, Victor. Papers, 1983-1986 (Box 59, Folder 6)
        - G244, Computer Music Journal. Background information,1983-1984 (Box 59, Folder 7)
        - G244, Computer Music Journal, v. 4 no. 3 and v. 5 no. 3 (Box 59, Folder 8)
        - G244, Computer Music Journal, v. 6 nos. 1, 3, 4 (Box 59, Folder 9)
        - G244, Computer Music Journal, v. 7 nos. 1, 2, 3 (Box 60, Folder 1)
        - G244, Computer Music Journal, v. 7 no. 4 - v. 8 no. 2 (Box 60, Folder 2)
        - G244, Computer Music Journal, v. 8 nos. 3-4 (Box 60, Folder 3)
        - G244, Computer Music Journal, v. 9 nos. 1-2 (Box 60, Folder 4)
        - G244, Computer Music Journal, v. 9 nos. 3-4 (Box 60, Folder 5)
        - G244, Computer Music Journal, v. 10 nos. 2, 3, 4 (Box 60, Folder 6)
        - G244, Computer Music Journal, v. 11 nos. 1-2 (Box 60, Folder 7)
        - G244, Computer Music Journal, v. 11 nos. 3-4 (Box 61, Folder 1)
        - G244, Computer Music Journal, v. 12 nos. 1-2 (Box 61, Folder 2)
        - G245, International Journal of Robotics Research, Brochure and v.1 nos. 1-2 (Box 61, Folder 3)
        - G245, International Journal of Robotics Research, v. 1 nos. 3-4 (Box 61, Folder 4)
        - G245, International Journal of Robotics Research, v. 2 nos. 1-4 (Box 61, Folder 5)
        - G245, International Journal of Robotics Research, v. 3 nos. 1-2 (Box 61, Folder 6)
        - G245, International Journal of Robotics Research, v. 3 nos. 3-4 (Box 61, Folder 7)
        - G245, International Journal of Robotics Research, v. 4 nos. 1-2 (Box 61, Folder 8)
        - G245, International Journal of Robotics Research, v. 4 nos. 3-4 (Box 61, Folder 9)
        - G245, International Journal of Robotic Research, v. 5 nos. 1-2 (Box 62, Folder 1)
        - G245, International Journal of Robotics Research, v. 5 no. 3 and v. 6 no. 2 (Box 62, Folder 2)
        - G245, International Journal of Robotics Research, v. 6 nos. 3-4 (Box 62, Folder 3)
        - G245, International Journal of Robotics Research, v. 7 nos. 1-3 (Box 62, Folder 4)
        - G246, Winston, Patrick and Michael J. Brady. Papers received, #1May 21 (Box 62, Folder 5)
          1984
        - G246, Winston, Patrick and Michael J. Brady. Papers received, #2May 21 (Box 62, Folder 6)
        - G246, Winston, Patrick and Michael J. Brady. Papers received, #3May 21 (Box 62, Folder 7)
        - G246, Winston, Patrick and Michael J. Brady. Papers received, #4May 21 (Box 62, Folder 8)
        - G246, Winston, Patrick and Michael J. Brady. Papers received Oct. 9, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 9)
        - G246, Winston, Patrick and Michael J. Brady. Annual report #11984 (Box 62, Folder 10)
        - G246, Winston, Patrick and Michael J. Brady. Annual report #21984 (Box 62, Folder 11)
        - G246, Winston, Patrick and Michael J. Brady. Annual report #31984 (Box 62, Folder 12)
        - G246, Winston, Patrick and Michael J. Brady. Annual report #41984 (Box 63, Folder 1)
        - G246, Winston, Patrick and Michael J. Brady. Annual report #51984 (Box 63, Folder 2)
        - G246, Winston, Patrick and Michael J. Brady. Annual report #61984 (Box 63, Folder 3)
        - G246, Winston, Patrick and Michael J. Brady. Annual report #71984 (Box 63, Folder 4)
        - G246, Winston, Patrick and Michael J. Brady. Annual report #81984 (Box 63, Folder 5)
        - G246, Winston, Patrick and Michael J. Brady. Annual report #91984 (Box 63, Folder 6)
        - G246, Winston, Patrick and Michael J. Brady. Annual report #101984 (Box 63, Folder 7)
        - G246, Winston, Patrick and Michael J. Brady. Annual report #111984 (Box 63, Folder 8)
        - G246, Winston, Patrick and Michael J. Brady. Matthew Thomas Mason, Manipulator Grasping and Pushing Operations, 1982 (Box 63, Folder 9)
        - G246, Winston, Patrick and Michael J. Brady. John Francis Canny, Finding Edges and Lines in Images, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 10)
        - G246, Winston, Patrick and Michael J. Brady. Richard H. Lathrop, Parallellism in Manipulator Dynamics, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 11)
        - G246, Winston, Patrick and Michael J. Brady. Patrick H. Winston and Karen A. Prendergast, The AI Business, 1984 (Box 64, Folder 1)
        - G246b, Winston, Patrick and J. Michael Brady. Papers (Box 64, Folder 2)
          1985-1986
        - G246b, Winston, Patrick and Michael J. Brady. Jonathan Hudson Connell, Learning Shape Descriptions: Generating and Generalizing Modules of Visual Objects,1985 (Box 64, Folder 3)
        - G246b, Winston, Patrick and Michael J. Brady. Margaret Morrison Fleck, Local Rotational Symmetries,1985 (Box 64, Folder 4)
        - G247, Vercoe, Barry. Papers, 1982-1988 (Box 64, Folder 5)
        - G248, Becker, Howard. Annual report #11984 (Box 64, Folder 6)
        - G248, Becker, Howard. Annual report #21984 (Box 64, Folder 7)
        - G248, Becker, Howard. Art World (Galley) #1 (Box 64, Folder 8)
        - G248, Becker, Howard. Art World (Galley) #2 (Box 64, Folder 9)
        - G248, Becker, Howard. Art World (Galley) #3 (Box 65, Folder 1)
        - G248, Becker, Howard. Art World (Galley) #4 (Box 65, Folder 2)
        - G249, Kendall, Gary. Papers, 1984-1987 (Box 65, Folder 3)
        - G249e, Kendall, Gary. Papers, 1985-1986 (Box 65, Folder 4)
        - G249f, Kendall, Gary. Papers, c. 1986 (Box 65, Folder 5)
        - G257, McGill, Michael. Proceedings of the Sixth Annual International ACM SIGIR Conference on Research and Development in Information Retrieval, 1983 (Box 65, Folder 6)
        - G275, Brady, J. Michael. International Symposium of Robotics Research. Prospectus and papers.1983 (Box 65, Folder 7)
        - G275, Brady, J. Michael. International Symposium of Robotics Research, Agenda materials #11983 (Box 65, Folder 8)
        - G275, Brady, J. Michael. International Symposium of Robotics Research, Agenda materials #21983 (Box 65, Folder 9)
        - G275, Brady, J. Michael. International Symposium of Robotics Research, Agenda materials #31983 (Box 65, Folder 10)
        - G275, Brady, J. Michael. International Symposium of Robotics Research, Agenda materials #41983 (Box 65, Folder 11)
        - G275, Brady, J. Michael. International Symposium of Robotics Research, Agenda materials #51983 (Box 65, Folder 12)
        - G275, Brady, J. Michael. International Symposium of Robotics Research, Agenda materials #61983 (Box 65, Folder 13)
        - G275, Brady, J. Michael. Robotics Research, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 1)
        - G276, Kendel, Eric and Richard Paul. Magazine article, May 1985 and book review, Jan. 1988 (Box 66, Folder 2)
        - G283, Perkel, Donald H. Models of Neurons, 1978 (Box 66, Folder 3)
        - G285b, Hearn, Anthony. Papers receivedJuly 9, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 4)
        - G285b, Hearn, Anthony. Papers receivedMay 11, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 5)
        - G297, Sproull, Lee. Papers, 1985-1987 (Box 66, Folder 6)
        - G301, Caviness, B. F. Papers received Apr. 19, 1984 (Box 67, Folder 1)
        - G303, Fox, Geoffrey. Papers, 1982 (Box 67, Folder 2)
        - G303, Fox, Geoffrey. Papers received, 1983 (Box 67, Folder 3)
        - G303, Fox, Geoffrey. Papers received Mar. 30, 1984 (Box 67, Folder 4)
        - G303, Fox, Geoffrey. Papers received #1July 16, 1984 (Box 67, Folder 5)
        - G303, Fox, Geoffrey. Papers received #2July 16, 1984 (Box 67, Folder 6)
        - G303, Fox, Geoffrey. Papers received #3July 16, 1984 (Box 67, Folder 7)
        - G303, Fox, Geoffrey. Annual report, v. 21983-1984 (Box 67, Folder 8)
        - G303, Fox, Geoffrey. Magazine article, 1985 (Box 67, Folder 9)
        - G303, Fox, Geoffrey. Solving Problems on Concurrent Processors (draft), cover letter and contents (Box 68, Folder 1)
        - G303, Fox, Geoffrey. Solving Problems on Concurrent Processors (draft), ch. 1 (Box 68, Folder 2)
        - G303, Fox, Geoffrey. Solving Problems on Concurrent Processors (draft), ch. 2-4 (Box 68, Folder 3)
        - G303, Fox, Geoffrey. Solving Problems on Concurrent Processors (draft), ch. 5-7 (Box 68, Folder 4)
        - G303, Fox, Geoffrey. Solving Problems on Concurrent Processors (draft), ch. 8-9 (Box 68, Folder 5)
        - G303, Fox, Geoffrey. Solving Problems on Concurrent Processors (draft), ch. 10 (Box 68, Folder 6)
        - G303, Fox, Geoffrey. Solving Problems on Concurrent Processors (draft), ch. 11-13 (Box 68, Folder 7)
        - G303, Fox, Geoffrey. Solving Problems on Concurrent Processors (draft), ch. 14-15 (Box 68, Folder 8)
        - G303, Fox, Geoffrey. Solving Problems on Concurrent Processors (draft), References and appendices (Box 68, Folder 9)
        - G303, Fox, Geoffrey. Solving Problems on Concurrent Processors, v. 1, 1988 (Box 68, Folder 10)
        - G305b, Shipp, William. Papers, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 11)
        - G305b, Shipp, William. Papers, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 12)
        - G305b, Shipp, William. Papers received Sept. 25, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 13)
        - G313, McMahon, Thomas. Papers, 1984 (Box 69, Folder 1)
        - G313, McMahon, Thomas. Muscles, Reflexes, and Locomotion, 1984 (Box 69, Folder 2)
        - G313, McMahon, Thomas. Papers received 1987 (Box 69, Folder 3)
        - G313, McMahon, Thomas. McKay's Bees, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 4)
        - G314, Nisbett, Richard. Draft of an untitled book about induction, ch. 1 (Box 69, Folder 5)
        - G314, Nisbett, Richard. Draft of an untitled book about induction, ch. 2 (Box 69, Folder 6)
        - G314, Nisbett, Richard. Draft of an untitled book about induction, ch. 3-4 (Box 69, Folder 7)
        - G314, Nisbett, Richard. Draft of an untitled book about induction, ch. 5-6 (Box 69, Folder 8)
        - G314, Nisbett, Richard. Draft of an untitled book about induction, ch. 7-8 (Box 69, Folder 9)
        - G314, Nisbett, Richard. Draft of an untitled book about induction, ch. 9-10 (Box 69, Folder 10)
          [NOTE: See related material for Grant #524a in Box II-101, folders 2-6]
        - G314, Nisbett, Richard. John H. Holland, Adaptation in Natural and Artificial Systems, 1975 (Box 69, Folder 11)
        - G318, Friedman, Daniel. Coordinated Computing: Tools and Techniques for Distributed Software, (draft), ch. 1-21982 (Box 70, Folder 1)
        - G318, Friedman, Daniel. Coordinated Computing: Tools and Techniques for Distributed Software, ch. 3-41982 (Box 70, Folder 2)
        - G318, Friedman, Daniel. Coordinated Computing: Tools and Techniques for Distributed Software, ch. 51982 (Box 70, Folder 3)
        - G318, Friedman, Daniel. Coordinated Computing: Tools and Techniques for Distributed Software, ch. 6.1-6.31982 (Box 70, Folder 4)
        - G318, Friedman, Daniel. Coordinated Computing: Tools and Techniques for Distributed Software, ch. 6.4-7.11982 (Box 70, Folder 5)
        - G318, Friedman, Daniel. Coordinated Computing: Tools and Techniques for Distributed Software, ch. 7.2-end1982 (Box 70, Folder 6)
        - G318, Friedman, Daniel. Coordinated Computing: Tools and Techniques for Distributed Software, 1984 (Box 70, Folder 7)
        - G327[a-d], Dolby, James. Papers, Apr. 1983 (Box 70, Folder 8)
        - G327[a-d], Dolby, James. Papers, May 1983 (Box 70, Folder 9)
        - G327[a-d], Dolby, James. Papers, Sept. 1983 (Box 70, Folder 10)
        - G327[a-d], Dolby, James. Papers, May 1984 (Box 71, Folder 1)
        - G327[a-d], Dolby, James. Final report, enclosures #1July 1984 (Box 71, Folder 2)